HEIDI HARTMAN

Address: #503-298 East 11th Ave, Vancouver, BC Email: heidihartman21@yahoo.com Phone: (778) 868-3386

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

An enthusiastic, forward-thinking professional with exceptional passion and talent for engaging and supporting change agents offering over 10 years of experience in managing social innovation events and projects, growing networks of entrepreneurs in Canada, the US and Russia, and building and maintaining relationships with diverse groups of people.

Core strengths include inspiring leadership, results-driven communication, a collaborative and inspiring team member, attention to detail, dedicated work ethic, positive energy, natural organizer, technically savvy and exceptional people skills focused on building community.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

July 2008 to Present

Hollyhock and Renewal

Vancouver, BC

SVI HOLLYHOCK PRODUCER

- Managed all event logistics for the past four Annual Social Venture Institutes (SVI) at Hollyhock (130-145 attendees) including agenda development, budget management, party planning, speaker confirmation and sponsor relations
- Fosters strong, lasting and meaningful connections among SVI alumni throughout the year by managing an email listserv for SVI Alumni and engaging alumni to host local gatherings

SOCIAL MEDIA & VANCOUVER MARKETING MANAGER

- Initiated and manage all Hollyhock's social media marketing including Facebook Page, Twitter, Flickr, YouTube and content on Hollyhock's blog
- Managed the production of hollyhocklife.org, a new Wordpress interactive blog for Hollyhock
- Coached Hollyhock presenters (over 100 each year) in best practices to promote their work and program with an emphasis on engaging their community through social networks
- Recruited, managed and trained five social marketing interns to support Hollyhock's online engagement strategy
- Expanded Hollyhock's brand and visibility in Vancouver by serving as the token Hollyhock staff person, engaging with the community and attending many key events

March 2005 to July 2008 Social Venture Network (SVN) San Francisco, CA SENIOR EVENT MANAGER

- Managed all event logistics for three Annual Member Gatherings (250-285 attendees), three Fall Conferences (275-325 attendees), and two Social Venture Institute (SVI) Women's Gatherings (70-90 attendees) including agenda development, budget management, venue relations, meal and entertainment planning, speaker confirmation and sponsor benefits
- Directed agenda and session development by negotiating diverse personalities on conference committees, considering hundreds of suggestions and requests with diplomacy and sensitivity
- Managed and mentored a team of 9 SVN staff to work together in an effective, cohesive and fun manner to produce increasingly high-quality events
- Recruited, managed and retained a diligent, hard working, positive team of volunteers for each conference
- Built genuine relationships with venue personnel and event vendors and served as a positive and effective change agent and educator on sustainable practices

July 2001 to March 2005 Center for Citizen Initiatives (CCI) San Francisco, CA MANAGER OF SPECIAL PROJECTS AND PUBLICATIONS

- Direct responsibility for all organizational event planning and execution: 2002 conference in St. Petersburg, Russia for 250 international attendees; 2004 conference in Washington, D.C. and Moscow, Russia for 100 international attendees
- Engaged Russian entrepreneurs to work together to explore solutions to help grow their businesses and reduce corruption
- Managed, created, distributed all organizational and program-specific publications and event marketing materials

EDUCATION

June 2001 University of Southern California, Los Angeles, CA

Bachelor of Arts: International Relations and Russian

August 2000 to **St. Petersburg State University**, St. Petersburg, Russia December 2000 Council Study Abroad Program